[cheering]
Thank you.
All right, we only have an hour.
[laughter]
Have I offended anybody yet? Good. You
will.
It'll happen. It happens fast.
We have gotten soft.
We have gotten soft. Watch this. What
are you allergic to?
Nothing. [laughter]
NOTHING.
Gluten wouldn't take down our
generation.
[laughter]
We're not allergic to things like
peanuts. You know why? Our parents made
us eat peanuts.
They made us eat peanuts until we
weren't allergic
TO PEANUTS.
[applause]
[cheering]
AND IF OUR THROATS STARTED to close up,
you know how they opened IT UP? THEY
SHOVED MORE PEANUTS DOWN IT.
I'M NOT ALLERGIC TO GERMS. Watch this.
Shake my hand. Look at that. THAT'S HOW
YOU SHAKE A HAND. I DON'T care about
germs. I Listen, I'm starting to really
hate people. Let me start out with that.
[laughter]
I went to shake a guy's hand the other
day. He goes, "Oh, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, I JUST WASHED."
[laughter]
THAT'S WHEN I WANT TO SHAKE YOUR HAND.
[applause]
NOT WHEN IT'S FILTHY. OH, OH, GOOD
TIMING. I I WAS ABOUT TO WASH. NOW I CAN
FIT ANOTHER SHAKE IN.
[laughter]
DO YOU SEE HOW CRAZY IT'S GOTTEN? I WAS
raised on germs, okay? Germs are good
for you. I DIDN'T WASH MY HANDS UNTIL I
WAS 22.
[laughter]
IN MY FAMILY, THERE WERE FIVE PEOPLE,
one sink, one hand towel.
Five people shared one hand towel that
NEVER DRIED.
[laughter]
IT'S STILL WET. WHEN I GO HOME, IT'S
STILL WET FROM 1989.
[applause]
AND I JUST FOUND OUT RECENTLY THAT none
of us ever touched the front of the
towel, cuz that's where we thought
everybody else was touching.
[laughter]
We all snuck around back. Turns out
that's where the polio, scabies, hip,
hand, foot, mouth, head, shoulders,
knees, and toes, KNEES, AND TOES DISEASE
WAS HANGING OUT.
WE DIDN'T HAVE ANTIBACTERIAL soap when I
WAS A KID. NO, THE OLD GERMS KILLED THE
NEW GERMS.
[applause]
[cheering]
WE DIDN'T HAVE THIS LITTLE WUSSY pump
soap that you guys
Can you say wussy? CAN YOU SAY WUSSY? I
don't want TO UPSET THE LITTLE
MILLENNIAL WORD POLICE.
OH, HORNY SAID WUSSY. HORNY SAID WUSSY.
HOW ABOUT THESE PEOPLE ON Twitter that
have five followers?
WHY DON'T YOU JUST TEXT EVERYBODY YOU
KNOW?
[applause]
[cheering]
I LIKE GERMS. Germs make you stronger.
We didn't even have pump soap. We had to
borrow soap. We had to borrow soap that
lasted so long, it rusted. It rusted.
It would crack and rust, and in the
cracks there were rivers of mud. THIS IS
WHAT YOU USED TO WASH your hands.
I have an immunity. I shake hands. I
don't care. I grew up in a time you're
not going to believe HOW OLD ARE YOU?
NO, THE KID WHAT IS THIS?
[laughter]
[applause]
HOW OLD ARE YOU? 12. 12?
[laughter]
THAT'S ADORABLE. LOOK AT HIM.
LET ME tell you something. WHAT'S YOUR
NAME? HUDSON. HUDSON?
[laughter]
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BELIEVE THIS.
I GREW UP IN A TIME, HUDSON, WHEN SALAD
BARS, THERE WAS NO GLASS.
[cheering]
[applause]
THERE WAS NOTHING IN between you and the
lettuce. IT WAS LIKE THE WILD WEST.
PEOPLE GOT RIGHT UP IN IT. YOU WATCHED
THEM. YOU WATCHED PEOPLE LIKE
[laughter]
THEY SPIT all over IT. THEY SPIT ALL
OVER IT, HUDSON, AND YOU ATE IT. YOU ATE
IT.
[applause]
THAT WAS THE PRICE YOU PAID FOR
UNLIMITED LETTUCE.
[laughter]
[applause]
[cheering]
NOW YOU CAN'T GET NEAR IT. THE THE SALAD
BAR It's like they they GOT THAT THAT
GLASS UP. YOU GOT TO YOU GOT TO LEAN IN
AGAINST THE GLASS. YOU'RE YOU'RE You're
You can't get near the lettuce, BUT YOUR
FACE IS WORKING this disgusting this Oh,
I'm going IN FOR THE BABY CORN. DOES
ANYBODY WANT BABY
HOLD MY FOOT. HOLD MY FOOT. I'M
I'M
I'M GOING TO I'M GOING TO LEVEL TWO YOGA
move trying to get the baby corn.
[laughter]
You know, WE USED TO TOUCH DOOR HANDLES
IN THE BATHROOM?
[laughter]
REMEMBER THAT? Wasn't so long ago.
Then all of a sudden everybody started
to take a paper towel like like they've
committed a crime and they're WIPING
PRINTS.
[laughter]
NOW WE GOT A PROBLEM, RIGHT? Cuz the eco
freako people
have taken away the paper towels.
THEY'RE MAKING US STICK OUR HANDS INTO
THIS DYSON.
HAND KIDNAP IT'S DANGEROUS. It's
dangerous. It
It throws your HAND AROUND AT 500 MILES
PER HOUR.
It's narrow and you get and you get and
you don't want to touch the side so it's
it's like that game Operation. It's like
[applause]
I touched the side. NOW I GOT TO
WASH THEM AGAIN.
I GOT IT THIS TIME. DAMN IT.
AND you still DON'T WANT TO TOUCH THE
DOOR HANDLE, RIGHT? So now now you got
to hang out in the bathroom like a
creep.
[laughter]
WAITING FOR SOMEBODY TO COME IN AND THEN
SLIDE BY HIM LIKE A CRAB LIKE A
SOME SORT OF military operation like I'M
I'M DOING CROSSFIT EXERCISES IN THE
BATHROOM.
[applause]
[laughter]
THIS IS SO
YOU HAVE TO CATCH UP. IT'S OKAY.
[laughter]
[applause and cheering]
Get a closer TO A MICROPHONE.
[laughter]
THIS IS THE WORLD
WE HAVE GOTTEN TOO SOFT.
WE HAVE GOTTEN too soft.
[laughter]
Now I've LOST MY PLACE.
[applause and cheering]
[applause]
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE WE GET IT ALL.
WELL, you don't have to zoom in on the
list, DO YOU?
[laughter]
CAN WE MAKE THIS LOOK SPONTANEOUS?
[applause]
[cheering]
YOU CAN'T GET ME SICK. You can't get me
sick.
[laughter]
We didn't have bottles of water when I
was a kid. Filtered water?
[laughter]
THAT'S WHAT YOUR KIDNEYS ARE FOR.
[applause]
WE DRANK OUT OF A HOSE.
[cheering]
[applause]
AND IT WASN'T EVEN OUR HOSE.
[laughter]
We went up to some house we didn't even
know and we just turned on the hose and
dirt flew out and spider eggs and
[laughter]
LEAD LEAD RUNS THROUGH MY VEINS.
WE HAD TO DRINK out of a hose because we
weren't allowed inside OF THE HOUSE
UNTIL 5:00 P.M.
[applause]
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE PARENTS WERE DOING
till 5:00 p.m.
cuz we weren't ALLOWED INSIDE OF THE
HOUSE
UNTIL 5:00 P.M.
OUR PARENTS EVERY DAY, THEY SAID, "GET
LOST. COME BACK AT 5:00."
AND IF WE DIDN'T COME BACK, YOU KNOW
WHAT THEY DID? THEY HAD ANOTHER KID.
[laughter]
[applause]
THEY DIDN'T KNOW WHERE WE WERE ALL DAY.
I WAS WITH MY FRIEND SHAWN. WE WERE
BIKING. HE GOT HIT BY A CAR.
[laughter]
WE THEN SAT OUTSIDE of his house UNTIL
5:00 P.M.
[applause]
UNTIL WE WERE ALLOWED IN. WE told his
parents and then they stitched him up.
[laughter]
WE HAVE GOTTEN SOFT. WE HAVE GOTTEN SOFT
TOUCH AND I DON'T even know if you're a
millennial or if you're you're post the
problem OF THE MILLENNIAL.
[laughter]
BUT THESE millennials are out here.
Where are people IN THEIR 20S?
THAT'S
THE MOST ANNOYING PEOPLE IN OUR SOCIETY.
[applause and cheering]
SOCIETY. These These Look at them. Look
at them. Look at this guy right here.
No, look at you.
[cheering and applause]
Yes, you. How old are you?
27. YOU ARE DUMB. YOU ARE DUMB.
[laughter]
HE'S SO DUMB, HE'S LAUGHING WHILE I'M
CALLING HIM DUMB.
[laughter]
I'M KIDDING. WHAT is your name, buddy?
My name is Perry. Perry, what a
MASCULINE NAME. UM
[laughter]
[cheering]
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING, PERRY. YOUR
GENERATION
CAME ONTO OUR PLANET
[laughter]
AND YOU RUINED IT.
YOU CHANGED TOO MUCH. And they're out
there right NOW JUDGING ME
[laughter]
ON A CRITERIA I DID NOT GROW UP WITH.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT GENDER I AM
ANYMORE.
[applause]
I MEAN, I'M NOT BEING FLIPPED. THERE'S A
LOT of new choices and I haven't done
all the research and you know,
[laughter]
maybe I fit into something else and I'm
fine with that. I'm I'm ready for a
change.
[laughter]
Millennials have taken away all the fun.
It's not fun anymore. Do you realize
that?
You can't Everything's got to be equal
for you guys. Everything's got to be
equal. Can't be a man in bed, can you?
WHAT'S WHAT'S THE FUN TALK FOR A
MILLENNIAL GUY LIKE? YOU'RE WITH A GIRL
LIKE, "OH, OH, ARE YOU MY LITTLE EQUAL?
WHO'S MY
[applause]
WHO'S MY LITTLE EQUAL? WHO'S MY STRONG
INDEPENDENT GET THAT GUY LAUGHING RIGHT
THERE. GET IT ON HIM. LOOK AT HIM.
I HAVEN'T HAD AN ERECTION SINCE THE
MILLENNIALS took over.
You have TO HAVE SEX ON THE SIDE SO
nobody's in a power position.
[applause]
These millennials came on to our planet.
You changed the way we sneezed.
[laughter]
For thousands of years, THIS
THIS WAS FINE.
[applause]
THIS THIS IS
[cheering]
THIS IS DUMB. THIS MAKES NO SENSE AT
ALL. THE hand was made for sneezing.
[laughter]
This is a perfect vessel. This ricochets
back in your face.
I got stuck in there one time.
IT DOESN'T WORK. I WASH MY HANDS SEVERAL
TIMES A DAY. I'VE NEVER
WASHED THIS.
[laughter]
[applause]
[cheering]
I I'VE NEVER SEEN SOMEBODY GO, "OH OH, I
JUST going to a PUBLIC RESTROOM. I I I
JUST I JUST sneeze into my There's not
even A NAME FOR THIS. MY
[laughter]
MY MILLENNIAL PIT. I JUST SNEEZED INTO
MY
[applause]
[laughter]
THEY'RE SO SENSITIVE and they all come
pre-installed with ADD.
[applause]
[laughter]
They all have ADD and they love to tell
you, "I HAVE ADD."
I'M LIKE, "YOU'RE LUCKY TO HAVE ADD in
this day and age with all these
distractions
Can you imagine having ADD in the 1600s?
[laughter]
Maybe a horse went by every 4 hours.
You're out They're out to They're
churning the butter. THIS THIS THIS
SUCKS. I I'VE GOT A DISORDER. SOMETHING
[laughter]
SOMETHING DISTRACT ME. WHAT WAS THAT? A
LEAF? NO, BACK to the the
I'm so glad I grew up before social
media. I I really I couldn't handle that
in high school.
[applause]
I feel bad for the young people. I mean,
you know
in high school I
I suspected I was a loser. Now
[laughter]
Now it would be digitally confirmed, you
know?
[cheering]
I can handle it as an adult, you know
what I mean? It's like
Hey, if it wasn't for social media, I
wouldn't know how much stuff I wasn't
being invited to.
[laughter]
They're too sensitive. Everybody's got
TO JUST CHILL OUT. Chill out. We've lost
our minds. And I'm not talking about the
gluten people. I'm not.
[laughter]
I have been going AFTER THE GLUTEN
PEOPLE now for 10 years. For 10 years.
People that have been watching me for
the last 10 years know I WAS ON TOP of
this this fad diet back when we thought
it WAS CALLED GLUTEN. BACK WHEN WE
THOUGHT IT WAS CALLED GLUTEN.
[applause]
IT'S A MARKETING scam to get you to buy
some products. Now, I know some people
actually have. Okay, so I know. Don't
don't don't go after ME ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
[laughter]
I KNOW SOME PEOPLE ACTUALLY HAVE you
know, cuz they come up to me after
shows. They're They're angry. They'll
come up and they'll go, um I don't think
it's funny that you uh
[laughter]
joke about celiac disease.
[applause]
Why is everybody laughing? Celiac
disease kills millions of people.
[laughter]
ALL I'M SAYING IS
IF it was real, I'd know how to
pronounce it. THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
I'M
[applause]
ALL I'M SAYING IS WE'VE been on this
planet for 200,000
years and the last 10, we all discovered
we can't eat wheat. It's
It's [applause] It's
[cheering]
[applause]
Do you know that sometimes if I eat a
walnut, my tongue gets a little itchy?
[laughter]
I've never told ANYBODY THIS.
[applause]
[cheering]
I JUST AVOID WALNUTS.
I had to Google how long we've been on
the planet for. Did you know the answer?
Yeah. Took me 3 days cuz I put in Google
how long the first thing it suggested
WAS BOILED CORN.
[laughter]
I'D LIKE TO KNOW THAT.
I DIDN'T know there was a recipe. I've
been guessing my whole life.
[laughter]
I just throw the CORN INTO A POT AND
EVERY few minutes I yell out, "DO YOU
THINK THE CORN IS READY?"
[laughter]
SO NOW I'M ON YOUTUBE watching videos
on HOW TO BOIL CORN.
[applause]
PEOPLE ARE MAKING VIDEOS ON HOW TO BOIL
CORN.
I'M LEAVING COMMENTS. COULDN'T STOP
WATCHING YOUR VIDEO
[laughter]
ON HOW TO BOIL CORN. RIVETING.
WATCHED ALL 12 MINUTES, EVEN THOUGH IT
ONLY TAKES EIGHT TO BOIL CORN.
[laughter]
LOOK AT THE VIDEOS ON HOW TO BOIL CORN.
THERE ARE SOME REAL LOSERS IN THIS
WORLD.
[applause]
I'M TELLING YOU, I'M TELLING you I've
been after this. I don't like fad diets.
I don't like fat like the the new ones
like the paleo diet. Do you know what
that is?
Yeah. You eat You eat whatever the
caveman ate.
Well, that makes a lot of sense since
they all died when THEY WERE 12.
[laughter]
[applause]
THESE IDIOTS ARE LIKE, "I'M GOING TO EAT
LIKE A CAVEMAN. I'm going to have IT
DELIVERED JUST LIKE THE CAVEMAN DID."
AND HOW DO WE even know the caveman was
skinny?
By the pictures they drew OF THEMSELVES
ON THE WALL?
I've never taken a fat picture of
myself.
I know the skinny angle.
[applause]
YOU YOU DON'T YOU DON'T THINK THE
CAVEMAN was deleting the the the the the
fat caveman self cave SELFIE SKETCH
THINGS? YOU DON'T?
[laughter]
I DON'T LIKE
FAD ANYTHING.
NOW, there's something called Prevagen.
Do you know what this is? It's a It's a
It's a supplement for memory loss and
it's an ingredient they recently
discovered in jellyfish. Because when
you think memory, YOU THINK JELLYFISH.
[laughter]
THESE THINGS BEACH THEMSELVES EVERY
SINGLE DAY.
And they can't find the ocean and it's
right BEHIND THEM.
GOING
THIS IS HOW RIDICULOUS WE'VE GOTTEN.
WE'VE GOTTEN RIDICULOUS. I WAS THROWN
OFF OF A TV station in Portland, Oregon
because I was making FUN OF GLUTEN.
[laughter]
I WAS IN PORTLAND, OREGON and I was on a
TV station and I uh
I said uh
I said gluten doesn't exist and the
anchor got really angry. She goes, "Yes,
it does."
I'm like, "Well, it scared me." I'm
like, "WELL, WHAT WHAT WHAT PROOF DO YOU
OH, BY THE WAY, this is in December,
just so you know for historical
purposes.
I go, "What what proof do you have?" She
said, "Because we have an entire section
IN THE STORE."
[laughter]
AND I SAID, "WELL, SO DOES SANTA CLAUS."
[applause and cheering]
[cheering]
[applause]
DOESN'T MAKE HIM real and they threw me
off. They were They got that angry.
People were commenting on their Facebook
page so fast, they threw me off and I
thought, "Well, that's it. Who Who
cares? It's Portland. WHO CARES?
[laughter]
NOBODY'S GOING TO EVER HEAR about it."
And then about 4 months ago, I was uh in
North Carolina.
Yeah. Are you from North Carolina?
[laughter]
Good. BY THE WAY, GOOD LUCK GETTING
unsweetened iced tea in North Carolina.
[laughter]
I I should have just stood up in the
restaurant AND YELLED, "WHO WON THE
CIVIL WAR?"
[laughter]
[applause]
GIVE ME A CUP OF WE WON UNSWEETENED,
PLEASE.
[laughter]
I'M IN NORTH CAROLINA, a guy comes up to
me in the street and it said, [laughter]
"Is it true
you don't believe IN SANTA CLAUS?
[laughter]
I GO, "THAT'S A WEIRD thing to ask
an adult
in June?"
[laughter]
I said, "Why are you asking me that?" He
said, "Because I read a story about how
you were kicked off of a TV station in
Portland on your Wikipedia page."
[laughter]
And that's when I realized ONE OF THESE
MILLENNIALS TOLD ON ME.
[applause]
SO, I went to my Wikipedia page and I
printed it out to show you tonight.
[laughter]
I know the the young people laugh. Like
at a show once somebody yelled out, they
go, "Oh, that's cute. You still print
stuff?"
[laughter]
Yeah, I'm in my 40s. I still print
stuff.
You know what else I do? I make plans a
week in advance and I KEEP THEM.
[cheering]
[applause]
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE I DO? WHEN I TAKE
SOMEBODY'S PICTURE, I COUNT TO THREE.
[laughter]
[applause]
YOUNG PEOPLE JUST HOLD UP THE CAMERA AND
THEN THEY WALK AWAY. LIKE
I thought you wanted a picture. They're
like, "I got 48." I'm like,
"Where was I FOR THAT?"
HERE'S MY actual Wikipedia page. This is
my actual Wikipedia page.
[applause]
And by the way,
I've been banned from making changes to
my own page.
[laughter]
I would change something, they go,
"What's your source?" I'M LIKE, "IT'S
ME."
[laughter]
ON DECEMBER 10TH, 2016,
Orny caused controversy on a local
Portland, Oregon
TV show by implying
Santa Claus WAS NOT REAL.
[laughter]
[applause]
NOW,
I DIDN'T IMPLY IT. I SAID IT.
[laughter]
BUT I'VE BEEN BANNED FROM making
changes.
HERE ARE THE ACTUAL COMMENTS people left
on the TV station's Facebook page. This
is AM Northwest. Ready? I'm going to
read you two comments.
Cathy Hunt says,
[laughter]
Well, she's going to call me out, I'm
going to CALL HER OUT.
[cheering]
[applause]
THAT'S H U N T. CATHY.
[cheering]
[laughter]
READY FOR THE NEXT
I WISH SOME PEOPLE WOULD BE more mindful
of what they say on morning TV.
My granddaughter just heard the
reference about no Santa Claus.
Thanks for opening up that can of worms.
[laughter]
I have changed the channel perhaps
forever if your guest don't clean up
their act ON MORNING TV.
[applause]
HOW MUCH HOW MUCH FUN IS THAT HOUSE?
[cheering]
Hey Cathy, maybe your granddaughter
should be in school. IT'S 10:00 A.M.
[laughter]
[applause]
AM NORTHWEST, the TV STATION RESPONDS.
[laughter]
HI CATHY, please tell your granddaughter
that Orny is just mad because he's on
SANTA'S NAUGHTY LIST.
[cheering]
[applause]
HOW OLD ARE WE?
Is that shaming? That feels like
shaming, by the way.
[laughter]
Then they start a hashtag COAL FOR ORNY.
[applause]
DEBORAH C. Talley says,
"HE'S AN IDIOT." UH I'M SORRY. T A L E
Y.
[laughter]
"He's an idiot. Making fun of people
with celiac disease is not funny or
cool. I wouldn't pay money to see him."
Then she does a hashtag coal for Orny.
[laughter]
SO, I GOT TO PUT AN END TO THIS RIGHT
AWAY. I GOT TO I got to do what people
do when they screw up in the spotlight.
I either either have to go into rehab
and I'm not giving up tequila or
[laughter]
or write a retraction. So, this is what
I wrote and I had to handwrite it in
after cuz they deleted it so fast.
[laughter]
Here's what I wrote. Earlier today, I
misspoke. And I want to be clear.
I know Santa exists
[laughter]
and has celiac disease.
[cheering]
[applause]
HASHTAG ORNY IS JEWISH.
I used to hate By the way, Orny Adams is
not my real name. I changed it when I
was in college. It was Adam Orenstein.
And by the way, that's one of the things
that that's what's wrong on my Wikipedia
page. They misspelled my legal name.
[laughter]
But I didn't I didn't I changed my name
because I didn't like people knowing I
was I was Jewish. It was like it was
weird. Like people
Some people don't like Jews. I don't
know if you know that.
[laughter]
I always thought, well, YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHY DON'T YOU HATE ME first for
something else? Then hate me because I'm
Jewish.
[laughter]
When I was younger, people people would
say anti-Semitic things. They'd come up
to you and go THEY'D GO, "YOU'RE CHEAP.
You're You're a Jew. You're a You're A
CHEAP JEW."
[laughter]
AND I SAID, "I'M SEVEN. I DON'T EVEN
HAVE MONEY YET."
[applause]
THESE GLUTEN PEOPLE.
[laughter]
[applause]
[cheering]
NO, WE'VE LOST OUR MINDS, OKAY? If we go
back to that PORTLAND BIT, WE
[laughter]
PEOPLE NEED TO JUST SETTLE DOWN. PEOPLE
need to just settle down. We're just
trying to have a a good time. There's
too many people on THE PLANET. THAT'S
THAT'S WHAT I'M starting to think. And
if the internet has taught us anything,
it's that half this planet needs TO BE
MEDICATED.
[applause]
AND BY THAT, I MEAN EUTHANIZED. I
[applause and cheering]
TIME TO GET RID OF SOME OF THESE PEOPLE.
I don't like mean people. I don't like
judgmental people. I don't LIKE PEOPLE
THAT DON'T LIKE people be people. I
DON'T LIKE VIOLENT PEOPLE. I DON'T LIKE
THAT'S RIGHT.
[applause and cheering]
YOU KNOW, LIKE LIKE THESE THESE MASS
SHOOTERS. WELL,
WOW, you got quiet. Are there
Are there any mass shooters here
tonight? That was weird. That
[laughter]
This is what I don't get about mass
SHOOTERS. AND I DON'T MEAN to make light
of something really serious, but these
people go into movie theaters and they
they shoot strangers. IF YOU'RE THAT
angry at the world, don't you know
people YOU'D RATHER KILL FIRST?
[applause]
SHOULDN'T THE STORY BE OH, OH, OH, AND
THEN HE INVITED EVERYBODY EVER HATED TO
A MOVIE and he SHOT THEM?
[laughter]
I'M NOT EVEN THAT ANGRY AT THE WORLD AND
I HAVE a list of 52 people.
[cheering]
53 53 PEOPLE AND A
[applause]
WE'VE GONE NUTS. THERE'S 7 BILLION
people on the planet. People need to
stop HAVING KIDS.
[cheering]
[applause]
HOW OFTEN DO YOU SEE SOMEBODY WITH A KID
and you think, "They shouldn't have HAD
A KID."
[laughter]
[applause]
WE DIDN'T NEED HIM. NOW WE GOT A LITTLE
VERSION OF HIM.
[applause]
THERE'S 7 BILLION people on this planet
and we're giving tax breaks to people
that have children.
How about rewarding the PEOPLE NOT
OVERPOPULATING THE PLANET?
[cheering]
[applause]
I should be able to cut out the UPC code
on my condoms, attach it to my 1040
form.
[laughter]
I want a rebate.
[applause]
You know this wasn't THE PLAN. YOU KNOW,
JUST A hundred years ago there was just
a billion people. God probably took a
little nap. Said, "Oh, everything's fine
on Earth. I'm going TO TAKE A LITTLE
NAP." WAKES UP, "WHAT ARE THEY DOING
DOWN THERE?"
[laughter]
7 BILLION PEOPLE, THEY'RE SLOTS.
GIVE ME THE BOOK. WHAT DID I TELL THEM?
BE fruitful and multiply. THAT'S A TYPO.
[laughter]
I SAID, "Be fruitful AND PULL OUT. WHY
WOULD I
[applause]
WE HAVE LOST OUR MINDS.
Do you know now because of the
gluttonians
[laughter]
everything has to have a warning label?
20 years ago there were no warning
labels, right? And and WE WERE FINE.
[laughter]
[applause]
[cheering]
THAT'S RIGHT, WE WERE FINE.
SURE, a few people died, but we didn't
need those people.
WATER HAS A WARNING LABEL.
[applause and cheering]
WATER HAS A warning label. Water. Water.
WATER. WATER. WATER. HOW MUCH WRITING IS
ON YOUR FAUCET?
HOW MUCH FIRST, LOOK AT all the writing
on this bottle of water. Look at it.
Look at it. Do you DO YOU SEE IT?
[laughter]
I DON'T LIKE YOU. LOOK AT THE WRITING ON
THIS BOTTLE of water. Look at it. Look
at this. LOOK AT THIS. LOOK AT THIS.
[cheering]
LOOK AT ALL THE WRITING ON THIS BOTTLE
of water. How much writing is on your
faucet? Zero. Zero.
[applause]
They're so afraid of being sued.
Everybody's suing everybody. I'm suing
four people myself right now.
[laughter]
These class action lawsuits, they're
great.
You don't even know you're suing
somebody until you check your mail and
there's a postcard.
[laughter]
Were you in Best Buy in 2012? I guess
so.
[applause]
Did you buy a flat screen TV? I THINK I
DID.
THEY MIGHT OWE YOU MONEY. I THINK THEY
DO.
[applause]
WHERE DO I SIGN THIS IMPORTANT POSTCARD?
THEN I TELL EVERYBODY, people like, "Oh,
you know, you look exhausted." I'm like,
"WELL, I'M SUING BEST BUY."
A lot of stress in my life.
We're going into closing arguments next
week.
Water has a warning. LOOK AT ALL THE
WRITING on a bottle of water. Warning,
DO NOT SWALLOW CAP.
[laughter]
[applause]
I THINK WE CAN AFFORD TO LOSE those
people, right?
Time to lose some of the cap swallowers.
Now we're down to 6.5 billion.
[laughter]
Do not refill. Because maybe some of us
will figure out the old stuff tastes a
lot LIKE THE NEW STUFF.
[laughter]
[applause]
THEY'LL PUT ANYTHING ON THERE TO PROTECT
THEMSELVES. WHAT? WARNING, THIS WAS
BOTTLED IN A FACTORY where there there
were once penis peanuts. Did I say
penis?
[laughter]
WARNING.
[cheering]
[applause]
WARNING, THIS WAS BOTTLED IN A FACTORY
[laughter]
where there WERE ONCE PEANUTS. AN OLD
peanut might have fallen into the water.
There's a There's a shellfish FACTORY
NEXT DOOR. SHELLFISH MIGHT HAVE WALKED
OVER AND DIPPED ITS TOE IN THE WATER.
[applause]
WARNING, THE GUY WHO BOTTLED THIS MAY
HAVE HAD X FOR BREAKFAST.
[laughter]
IF YOU'RE PREGNANT, ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF
YOU CAN DRINK WATER.
MAY OR MAY NOT CONTAIN WATER.
[laughter]
IF YOU'RE STILL READING THIS, GET HELP.
[applause]
AND WATER HAS an expiration date.
WATER IT CAN'T EXPIRE.
[applause]
IT CAN EVAPORATE.
If you open it up and there's nothing in
there,
it went bad.
[laughter]
But as long as there's SOMETHING IN
THERE, NOBODY'S EVER GONE,
"SHIT!
It's sour.
Don't drink the water."
[laughter]
IT SAT IN THE LAKE FOR thousands of
years.
These people put it in a bottle. YOU
HAVE 3 MONTHS TO FINISH IT, THEN THROW
IT OUT.
[laughter]
This is the world that's gone crazy.
Does any of this make sense to you yet?
I love the way you smile. It's just It's
so effortless. It just pops up.
[laughter]
IT REALLY DOES.
THAT'S what I call A PRE-MORTGAGE SMILE.
[cheering]
[applause]
YOU SMILE SO EASILY, LIKE you and me. It
takes like a second. Like we go to smile
and then the the the the the world drags
our lips down and
[laughter]
I get nervous every time I go to smile
because when I was a kid, I smiled at a
girl and I got nervous and my lip dried
and it got stuck on my teeth and
[cheering]
and every time I go to smile, I think
that's going to happen. I'm like, "It's
going to get stuck. I'm going to
[laughter]
But you're great, dude. It really I just
love how how much fun you have and how
carefree you are and you have like a
nice little sparkle in your eye.
You probably STILL HAVE DREAMS.
[applause]
YOU [cheering] THINK THESE PEOPLE HAVE
DREAMS ANYMORE?
NO, WE HAVE FLASHBACKS.
[applause]
[cheering]
WE HAVE flashbacks to where it all went
wrong.
[laughter]
When you're in your 20s, you think, "I'M
NOT GOING TO end up like these old
people. I'm going to live forever. I'm
never going to be the the the guy who
wears a HAWAIIAN SHIRT ALL YEAR LONG."
[laughter]
[applause]
THAT'S MY FAVORITE TYPE OF GUY, where
they just get old and they go, "Screw
it. I'm going Hawaiian shirt all year
long."
[applause]
Take me to Tommy Bahama's. Give me the
whole lineup.
There's a lot of them. There's the one
back there. Here's a third one.
Oh my god, my audience has turned into a
Jimmy BUFFETT CONCERT.
[applause]
I BETTER BE NICER TO THE MILLENNIALS.
[laughter]
WHEN YOU'RE YOUNG, YOU WANT TO KNOW WHY
you get thick when you get older? Food
becomes the last joy you have left.
[laughter]
When I'm done eating, I'm depressed
because I'm the furthest away from
eating again.
[laughter]
You know what I'm saying?
I JUST LOVE HOW
EXCITED YOU ARE. I think You look at a
guy like this. This is a guy who's
You've been through something. You can
just SEE IT ON YOU.
[applause]
PROBABLY DIVORCED, RIGHT? There you go.
Yep, THERE YOU GO.
[applause]
KID, PROBABLY HAVE A KID, RIGHT? YEP,
THAT that kid ruined your face. That's
what happened. That kid
[applause]
How old are you?
55.
55, I thought you were older. Okay,
[laughter] I am
NO, NO, NO. LOOK AT ME. LOOK AT ME. LOOK
AT ME. NO WIFE, no kids. I'm 64 years
old.
[cheering]
[applause]
People that are married and have kids,
they always look down on people like me.
They always say, "We We figured it out.
HE NEVER LET ME TELL YOU WHAT I HAVE
that you GUYS DON'T HAVE."
SILENCE.
[applause]
I WAKE UP EVERY DAY. I'M LIKE, "WHAT
WHAT'S THAT I'M NOT HEARING? WHAT IS
THAT?"
[laughter]
I LOOK DOWN. EVERYBODY'S SAFE. ON WITH
MY SELFISH DAY.
[applause]
YOU DIDN'T THINK YOUR LIFE WAS GOING TO
TURN out like this, did you? No. No. No.
[laughter]
NONE OF US DO. NONE OF US DO. That's
what life does to you. But, this is what
you're supposed to be Have the the
arrogance of youth. I love it. You
probably have a lot of friends still,
right? That you hang out with and laugh
and have a good time. NOT THE OLD
PEOPLE.
WHY DO YOU THINK THEY'RE HERE TONIGHT?
They have TO PAY A PROFESSIONAL TO
LAUGH.
[applause]
[cheering]
I JUST RAN INTO A MIC STAND ON MY
SPECIAL. YOU THINK MY LIFE TURNED OUT
THE WAY I WANTED IT TO?
I'VE LOST ALL MY FRIENDS TO MARRIAGE,
KIDS, SOBRIETY,
[laughter]
gluten allergies.
I'm down to three friends. Two I don't
even like.
[laughter]
[cheering]
One I'm hanging onto just in case I need
a kidney someday.
I've got a friend for parts.
[laughter]
I called him kidney once by accident.
I was like, "Hey, kidney Kenny." did he
Did he [laughter] hear that, did he?"
Is that Kenny?
[applause]
You'll see what happens to you. You'll
see.
[laughter]
How old are you, Kenny? 29. 29. Yeah,
YOU'RE DUMB, TOO.
[applause]
LIFE IS GOING TO DESTROY YOU.
[laughter]
I wake up every day I think, "Why did I
drink last night?"
And I DIDN'T EVEN DRINK.
I HAVE FELT HUNGOVER FOR THE last 10
years,
[laughter]
every
single day.
When you're 29, you think, "I'm not
going to end up like these OLD PEOPLE.
I'M GOING TO BE RELEVANT FOREVER. I'm
going to have the perfect life. I'll
never BE IN THE HOLE TO THE IRS or to
the bank, and I'm going TO MARRY THE
PERFECT GIRL." THAT'S what you think,
right? Yeah, and we're going to have
perfect kids, AND AND SHE WOULD NEVER
CHEAT ON ME.
[laughter]
AND THEN LIFE IS LIKE, "GET IN THE HOLE.
GET IN THE HOLE. GET IN THE
[cheering]
[applause]
[cheering and applause]
[cheering]
[applause]
GET IN THE HOLE.
[cheering]
[laughter]
I'LL NEVER HAVE MY MOM'S HIPS. GET IN
THE HOLE.
[laughter]
WE WAKE UP EVERY single day in a hole.
We just want to be at street level. We
just want to wake up even, not feel
sore, not feel any pain. That's all we
want.
Oh my god.
[laughter]
Can I breathe yet?
[applause and cheering]
I like getting older.
I really do. You have something to look
forward to. Do you know what I mean?
It's just It's nice to see the finish
line. It really is.
[laughter]
I almost signed up for the military last
year by accident. Um
anybody else ever do that?
[laughter]
Anybody here serve?
THANK YOU FOR YOUR SERVICE. YEAH,
[cheering]
I SAID IT. I SAID IT FIRST.
[applause]
I'M ALWAYS THE FIRST TO SAY IT. I like
to be first cuz then it feels like I get
the most credit for it.
[laughter]
I was at I was at the mall. I saw the
service people coming at me. I went,
"THANK YOU FOR YOUR SERVICE."
AND THEN AS I GOT CLOSER, I REALIZED
they were Girl Scouts in in the uniform.
Better safe than sorry, right?
What branch?
Army. Army. There you go. Thank you.
Thank you.
[applause]
How old were you when you went in?
18. That's amazing. That really is. That
takes a lot of courage. As I get older,
I realize how much courage it really
takes to go in at that age. I I I I
didn't have it. I I never even thought
about serving, but last year I was in
Salt Lake City, Utah.
And a guy comes running out of the
recruitment center. He's on the other
side of a parking lot. He scared me. HE
GOES, "BRO!
[laughter]
WANT TO JOIN THE ARMY?"
I THOUGHT, "WHO ARE YOU TALKING TO?" HE
GOES, "YOU!"
[laughter]
I SAID, "I HAVEN'T EVEN HAD MY MORNING
coffee yet."
I can't do anything before I have
coffee. I can't even make coffee until
I've had a cup of coffee. I MEAN
[applause]
SOME SOMETIMES I HAVE TO MAKE A CRAPPY
batch just to get to the good batch.
[laughter]
So he said HE GOES, "WANT TO JOIN THE
ARMY?" AND HE WAS HE WAS DRESSED IN
THOSE camouflaged fatigues. He scared
me. And I I said, "First of all,
I CAN SEE YOU."
[laughter]
WHAT
WOULDN'T IT HELP THE SALES PITCH IF you
wore camouflaged like a car bumper or
something?
I SAID I'M SAID I'M I'M TOO OLD. HE
SAID, uh "How old are you?" I go, "I'M
IN MY 40S." He goes, "YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE IN YOUR 20S."
I GO, "DO I LOOK AS DUMB AS KENNY?"
[laughter]
[applause]
I NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT SERVING, BUT LAST
YEAR WHEN THAT GUY SAID TO ME, "DO YOU
WANT TO SERVE?" For the first time in my
life, I thought, "Yeah, I do."
And that's when I realized we're
recruiting THE WRONG PEOPLE.
LET THE YOUNG PEOPLE ENJOY THEIR LIVES.
SEND PEOPLE like me OVER THERE. I'VE
LIVED long enough. I DON'T GIVE A
ANYMORE. I'M READY TO DIE.
[applause]
I KNOW WHAT WE'RE FIGHTING FOR.
I'VE GOT THE FIGHTING IN MY BELLY. I
WANT TO START THE FIGHTING 40S BRIGADE.
[applause]
I WANT TO PUT BOOTS ON THE GROUND with
ankle supports.
[laughter]
We'll be the greatest army in the world
because we won't care. BUNCH OF WE'LL
RUN RIGHT AT THE ENEMY. BUNCH OF OLD
GUYS IN A HAWAIIAN SHIRT RUNNING RIGHT
SHOOT ME. SHOOT ME FIRST. I'M SICK OF
LIFE. WE'LL HAVE OUR FLIP-FLOPS GOING
FLIP-FLOP FLIP-FLOP FLIP-FLOP. THEY'LL
HEAR US COMING A MILE AWAY.
MY DAD JUST TURNED 70. We bought him an
iPad for his birthday.
That is the cruelest thing
you can do to an old person.
[laughter]
The whole time he's going, "WHERE DID IT
GO?
EVERYTHING MOVED."
[laughter]
THEN MY 4-year-old nephew waddles over,
touches something, "Okay, it's back."
My 4-year-old nephew is tech support
[laughter]
[applause]
for my dad.
The kid's a genius. He takes my iPhone.
I think he's just touching the screen.
He He found the App Store. He's He's
downloading kid apps.
He cracked my passcode.
[laughter]
IT'S A THUMB PRINT.
WHEN ARE WE GOING THUMB PRINT ON
EVERYTHING? Cuz these passwords ARE
GETTING HARD. WHEN DID websites start
judging the quality
[applause and cheering]
of our passwords?
Weak.
[laughter]
That's pathetic. You call that a
passcode? Come on, get to good. Get to
good.
Meanwhile, my bank card, the one thing
that has all my money, is four numbers.
[laughter]
[applause]
But my Hilton Honors award account
has a footprint, an exclamation mark,
something as silly.
[laughter]
God forbid somebody hacks that and gets
a free night AT THE LOUISVILLE HILTON ON
ME.
[applause]
HAVE YOU NOTICED THE OLDER YOU GET, THE
further back in the pharmacy you go?
When you're a kid, you don't even go
inside. You're out front riding that
horsey for 50 cents. Next thing you
know, you're up against the back wall
with the walker balls and the diabetes
socks and pill cases so you know what
day of the week it is.
[laughter]
I'm sure eventually a wall opens up and
it just sucks you into an old age home.
[laughter]
It's probably right next to that chair
where you get your blood pressure taken.
[laughter]
If the if the reading's too high, the
chair probably just starts going back.
[applause]
Grab a thing of Grape-Nuts on the way
out.
[laughter]
That's how you know it's over. If you're
eating Grape-Nuts, that's the end of the
line.
There's no hope in that. It's a It's a
black and white cover with a piece of
dead wheat.
[laughter]
The prize inside is reading glasses.
Every time I see people in the blood
pressure chair, the old people, I THINK,
"WHOSE BRIGHT idea was it to convince
old people to sell their homes, move
into an RV, and drive across the
country?
[laughter]
They're losing their eyesight AND THEIR
REFLEXES. LET'S PUT them in the biggest
vehicle THEY'VE EVER BEEN IN."
[applause]
I SEE THOSE THINGS COMING, I GET THE
HELL OUT OF THE WAY. I treat it like an
ambulance. I'll drive up ON YARDS AND
[laughter]
THIS IS THE WORLD AND WE'RE all the
same. We are really all the same. I
realized this the other day. I was in
Target. You ever go to Target? Yes.
Yeah.
[applause]
I love Target. First of all, I'm
overwhelmed when I go in there. There's
too many choices.
FOR HOW MANY DIFFERENT SIZE ZIPLOC BAGS
DO WE NEED?
THERE'S AN ENTIRE AISLE. WHEN I WAS A
KID, THERE WAS ONE SIZE. If you didn't
like it, YOU WENT LIKE THIS.
[laughter]
NOW THEY HAVE SNACK, SNACK PLUS, QUART,
GALLON, 3 gallon, jumbo, triple jumbo.
They have one for the whole house. You
put the whole HOUSE IN A BAG and you zip
it up.
[applause]
Freezer? Freezer? They'll do anything to
SELL YOU MORE BAGS. FREEZER? DON'T PUT
THE ROOM TEMPERATURE ONES IN THE
FREEZER.
[laughter]
THAT'S GOING TO VOID the warranty.
EVERY YEAR THEY COME OUT WITH a new
style. The This year they have easy open
flaps.
WHICH MEANS SOME PEOPLE COULDN'T FIGURE
OUT THE ZIPPER.
[laughter]
[applause]
THIS WAS TOO HARD FOR SOME PEOPLE.
PEOPLE WERE WRITING IN, "MAKE IT EASIER.
MAKE IT EASIER." [laughter]
The Tide detergent aisle, the First of
all,
[laughter]
this is what's wrong with this country.
We have scented trash bags.
[laughter]
If your trash smells like trash,
TAKE IT OUT.
[applause]
ROTTEN FOOD PLUS Febreze smells like
rotten FOOD PLUS FEBREZE.
[applause]
THERE'S SO MANY DIFFERENT detergents you
can buy now. The the the the aisle, the
Tide detergent aisle, there's a million
different scents. There used to be one
scent, original.
[laughter]
Now you got like April Fresh. THEY'RE
MAKING SCENTS UP.
MONTHS DON'T SMELL.
[laughter]
NOBODY'S EVER GONE, "OH, I SMELL LIKE
NOVEMBER. HOW DO I
HOW DO I GET THAT APRIL FRESH SMELL?"
[applause]
I LOVE THE PEOPLE IN THE TIDE DETERGENT
aisle cuz this Well, this is everybody.
EVERYONE'S JUST SMELLING. EVERYONE'S
[laughter]
AND THEN WHEN THEY FIND THE ONE THEY
LIKE, THEY PUT IT BACK AND THEY GRAB A
NEW ONE FROM the back. We are all the
same. We are all the same. We are all
the same.
[cheering]
EVERYBODY IS THE [applause] SAME.
[applause]
I WENT INTO TARGET. Listen to this.
There's no common sense. We've lost our
minds. We have gotten SO DUMB. I SAW a
guy on a reality show. This is what he
said. He goes, "I'm going to turn my
life around 360°."
[applause]
Dude, he'll be right back. We are
starting, you idiot.
[laughter]
You go 180, you stop. You go 360, your
life's gone full circle. WHAT
ONCE YOU GO 720, GO GO
GO 1080. JUST KEEP GOING AND
in circles till you pass out from your
dumb.
I saw a guy on another reality show. He
was so drunk, he he did he goes, "I'm so
drunk, I'm abbreviated."
[laughter]
Not inebriated, abbreviated.
He's inebriated. His time on TV should
be abbreviated.
[applause]
I mean, we laugh about it, BUT IT'S A
SERIOUS PROBLEM because the little kids
are watching so much TV and you're
picking UP SECOND-HAND DUMB.
[applause]
I WENT INTO TARGET. I WENT into Target.
Ready for this?
I went into Target.
Bought a bunch of stuff. Used a coupon.
Paid with my American Express. The guy
goes, "Sir, sir, I need to see your ID."
I go, "Well, what for?" He goes, "Well,
you know, to make sure the card ISN'T
STOLEN."
[laughter]
I SAID, "I JUST USED A COUPON."
WHY WOULD I USE A COUPON
if the CARD WAS STOLEN?
[laughter]
[applause]
OH, YOU GOT ME THERE.
I'M BUSTED. 15 MINUTES AGO I MUGGED A
GUY. I FELT BAD. I WANTED to save him 75
cents on
April Fresh Tide.
[laughter]
There's no common sense. It's like every
year my cable bill goes up by like $100
and I have to call and threaten to
leave.
[laughter]
I'm not even nice anymore. I just call
them up. I go, "Lower the bill."
[laughter]
They go, "Who is this?" I GO, "IT'S ME.
NOW LOWER THE BILL."
They go, "How do we know? What's your
social? WHAT'S WHAT'S WHAT'S YOUR STREET
ADDRESS? WHAT'S YOUR" I SAID, "I'M
CALLING TO LOWER THE BILL. I'M SORRY.
ARE PEOPLE STEALING PEOPLE'S IDENTITIES
CALLING UP AND LOWERING THEIR CABLE
BILLS?"
[applause]
IS THIS SOME SORT OF EPIDEMIC I don't
know about? LOWER MY BILL.
[laughter]
PUT THAT IN THE NOTES. IF ANYBODY CALLS
TO LOWER ERNIE'S BILL,
LOWER [screaming] IT.
I DON'T CARE IF SOMEBODY CALLS BY
ACCIDENT. LOWER THE BILL.
THEY DON'T HAVE TO KNOW MY MOTHER'S
MAIDEN NAME, my my shoe size, my first
pet's pet that they They could call BY
ACCIDENT. MY NEXT CALL TO YOU GUYS BE,
"WELL, WELL, WELL, WHY DID MY BILL GO
DOWN?" OH, "SOME 12-YEAR-OLD NAMED
HUDSON CALLED UP DURING RECESS.
[applause]
THERE'S NO COMMON SENSE. I find myself
every day making this face. EVERY DAY
JUST GO,
[applause]
[laughter]
YOU EVER CATCH SOMEONE DOING SOMETHING
DUMB AND YOU ROLL YOUR eyes and they
don't catch you rolling your eyes? So
now you have to re-roll them even
louder. [laughter]
[applause]
What?
THERE'S NO COMMON SENSE. I GOT A ticket
cuz the thieves in Los Angeles are
stealing off of our license plates, the
little registration year sticker.
Yes, and you DON'T KNOW YOUR STICKER'S
MISSING.
[laughter]
CUZ YOU DON'T GO OUT TO YOUR CAR EVERY
MORNING and go, "IS MY STICKER STILL
THERE?"
[laughter]
YOU DON'T KNOW UNTIL YOU GET A TICKET.
SO I called the DMV. I said, "Hey,
there's a mix-up. I got a ticket but my
car is registered." And then she goes,
"Sir? Sir? You need to prove to us that
your car is registered." I said, "I'm
sorry. Am I talking TO THE DMV?"
[applause]
ISN'T THAT A LITTLE PIECE OF INFORMATION
you should have?
She goes, "Sir, it's policy. You need to
send us a copy of your registration." I
said, "I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE THAT IS."
[laughter]
She said, "We'd be happy to send YOU A
COPY."
[applause]
TO SEND BACK TO US. This is the
WORLD THAT I LIVE IN.
[applause]
I DIDN'T EVEN OPEN UP THE ENVELOPE. I
just wrote return to sender.
[laughter]
[applause and cheering]
Every day is a fight. It's a struggle.
My printer broke. I call a I call
customer service. BY THE WAY, HAVE YOU
NOTICED when your cable goes out, they
don't try and fix it? The first thing
they do is they try and bundle you.
[laughter]
Oh, we notice you don't have phone
service with us. Would you like phone
SERVICE WITH US? NO, CUZ THEN I wouldn't
be able TO MAKE THIS PHONE CALL RIGHT
NOW. I WAS
[laughter]
FIX MY CABLE, THEN SELL ME STUFF.
I like when you call up and the first
thing you hear is, "Please listen
carefully as our menu options have
changed."
If your customers are memorizing your
menu options,
[laughter]
FIX YOUR PRODUCT.
[applause]
[cheering]
MY PRINTER BROKE. I CALL HP. The first
thing they say, "Is it plugged in?"
[laughter]
Oh, yeah. I'm an adult. Did I Did I call
the kiddie line? Is this
[laughter]
The guy got nervous. He goes, "Well, can
I ask you what What are you using THE
PRINTER FOR?"
[laughter]
OH, I'M USING IT TO IRON. IS THAT THE
PROBLEM?
[laughter]
I MAKE A FLAPJACK. SOMETIMES I OPEN THE
HOOD. I PUT THE BATTER in there and then
I hit print with my foot. AM I USING IT
WRONG? FIX MY PRINTER.
[applause]
EVERY DAY IS A FIGHT. Every day is a
struggle.
I got INTO I GOT INTO A FIGHT with the
waitress. I asked her I I go, "What's
good on the menu?" And then she didn't
suggest anything I wanted. So, I had to
have that discussion with her.
I said, "How's the burger?" She goes, "I
don't know. I don't eat meat."
[laughter]
Now, she's going to turn my meal into a
political protest.
She goes, "I'm a vegan." You know how
they say it all judgmental sometimes?
"I'm a vegan."
I go, "WELL, I'M A ME AGAIN."
[applause]
YOU KNOW WHAT I TOLD HER? YOU KNOW WHY I
EAT MEAT? Because we made it to the top
of the food chain.
That's right. The cow had a chance to
stand up and learn a language like us,
BUT THE COW STAYED DOWN. THE COW STAYED
DOWN.
[applause]
YOU KNOW WHY I EAT MEAT? WHAT'S IN THE
WORD MEAT? EAT.
[laughter]
The word is actually me eat. It couldn't
be any clearer
unless they added the EXTRA E.
[applause and cheering]
ME EAT.
[applause]
THAT'S PROBABLY HOW IT GOT its name. One
day a caveman chewing on a bison leg,
the other one is like, "UH, WHAT WHAT'S
THAT?" ME EAT.
[laughter]
ME WANT ME EAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S IN THE WORD VEGAN?
NOTHING.
[laughter]
IT'S PROBABLY SHORT FOR VEGETABLES
AGAIN.
[applause]
EVERY DAY IS A FIGHT. That's why I like
doing this. When I'm up here, this is
the only part of my day that feels
right. This is This is justice for me.
The rest of the day is a fight. IT'S A
STRUGGLE.
[applause]
PEOPLE DON'T LISTEN TO ME during regular
hours.
[laughter]
I say stuff, I get in trouble all the
time. People don't love me the way you
GUYS LOVE ME.
[cheering]
[applause]
THIS THIS IS JUSTICE. THIS IS JUST I WAS
IN Chicago and a guy came up to me and
he said, "Seven years ago, I saw you for
the first time and I've come back every
single year to see you with the woman I
met on a blind date that first night.
And we now have a three-year-old kid.
And in that moment, I realized how
little I have gotten done in the last 7
years.
[applause]
This is justice. I don't have this in my
real life dating.
My last relationship ended because well,
we were different. I I was a morning
person and SHE WAS NUTS.
[laughter]
COMPLICATED. DO I HAVE TO SAY
COMPLICATED NOW? DO I have to clean it
up for THE STUPID LITTLE MILLENNIALS and
say she was complicated. SHE WAS
COMPLICATED.
[screaming]
SHE WAS NUTS.
[applause]
I WAS ALWAYS IN TROUBLE. LISTEN, I
thought I was being romantic one night.
Ready for this? Everything was mean. She
was always you're mean. You're mean.
Even when I wasn't being mean.
Look at her put her arm around him. YOU
SAY THAT TO HIM all the time. Is he
mean? Is he mean? You get it all the
time. ALL THE TIME. WE'RE NOT EVEN BEING
MEAN, are we?
[laughter]
I said to HER, I GO, "HEY, DO YOU MIND
putting the half and half away?" SHE
GOES, "YOU'RE MEAN."
[laughter]
I DIDN'T SAY, "HEY, THE HALF AND HALF
DOESN'T PUT ITSELF AWAY every day."
I thought that, BUT I DIDN'T SAY IT.
[applause]
I THOUGHT I WAS BEING ROMANTIC ONE
NIGHT. Ready for this? We're We're
cuddling and she's very petite and
beautiful. I go, "You're so soft. IT'S
LIKE CUDDLING WITH A MARSHMALLOW."
[laughter]
I KNOW IT'S WRONG NOW.
[applause]
DUMB ME, I THOUGHT I WAS BEING CUTE AND
ROMANTIC, YOU
Until I got the look. Women, when you do
something wrong, you get the look the
look they just their neck SNAPS BACK
LIKE
[laughter]
THEY COULDN'T BE FURTHER AWAY FROM YOU.
I just start backpedaling. I'm like like
a SIZE TWO MARSHMALLOW LIKE
[laughter]
A STALE SIZE TWO marshmallow like strong
independent stale marshmallow that we
have sex on THE SIDE MARSHMALLOW LIKE
I'M A MARSHMALLOW. I'M A STUPID
MARSHMALLOW LIKE
[applause]
WANT TO KNOW THE last thing she said to
me
when we broke up? The last thing is I'm
getting the keys back to my house. Now
people say things in the heat of the
moment.
This was bad.
[laughter]
She looked at me and she said, "Do you
want to know why you never made it as a
comedian?"
BECAUSE YOU'RE MEAN.
[applause]
AND I THOUGHT, "WELL, THANK GOD SHE
THINKS I'M FUNNY." CUZ YOU
[laughter]
MEAN I CAN FIX. FUNNY YOU KIND OF GOT TO
BE BORN WITH THAT.
That would have broken my heart. She's
like, "You didn't make it cuz YOU'RE NOT
FUNNY." THAT THAT WOULD HAVE DEVASTATED
ME.
[laughter]
We're not that smart, women. If you want
to live a happy life, okay? Take the
marshmallow example, okay? If you want
to be happy with him that you think is
mean sometimes and you want to be happy
you want to be happy, right? IT IS SO
SIMPLE.
ALL WOMEN HAVE to do to be happy IN THIS
LIFETIME
WHATEVER YOUR EXPECTATION
OF MAN IS, LOWER IT.
[applause and cheering]
[applause]
THAT'S IT. LOWER IT TO THE GROUND. Lower
it. Lower your bar. Lower your bar.
Lower your bar of men. We can meet
ground. We can meet ground. We wake up
in the HOLE EVERY DAY ANYWAY. We'll just
stay there.
WE'RE NOT THAT SMART, MEN. WHY DO YOU
THINK our shirts have pockets on the
outside?
So we know IT'S ON RIGHT.
[laughter]
[applause]
I MET A GUY ONCE, HE DROVE A TRUCK. I
was just trying to make conversation. I
go, "What do you What do you drive? An
F-150?" He goes, "250."
[laughter]
I go, "What's the difference?" He goes,
"A hundred."
[applause]
That's my people. THAT'S MY PEOPLE.
LOWER THE BAR.
AND WE'RE ARROGANT. Every time I go out
with my married friends, if a beautiful
woman walks by, one of them will go,
"Ooh,
man, if I wasn't married." If you
weren't married, WHAT?
[applause]
I KNEW YOU WHEN YOU WEREN'T MARRIED.
YOU WEREN'T GETTING THAT.
[applause]
THAT'S WHY YOU GOT MARRIED.
[laughter]
ARE YOU GOING to go not get her number
like you used TO WHEN YOU WEREN'T
MARRIED?
[laughter]
MARRIED MEN, THEY LIKE TO THEY LIKE TO
LOOK at other women, and when they get
caught, they say things like, "Well, I'm
not dead." Yes, you are.
[laughter]
SEE, THAT'S WHAT'S WRONG WITH MEN. We
see virility and living as getting
women. WOMEN ARE MORE EVOLVED. YOU WANT
TO SETTLE DOWN, RIGHT? YOU WANT the
white picket fence. We see that fence,
WE THINK, "SHIT, I GOT TO PAINT THAT
EVERY YEAR."
[applause]
WE CAN'T BE WHAT you want us to be. You
want that romantic guy, the guy in the
movies, every kiss begins with K guy.
[laughter]
That guy has ruined more relationships.
You want to know what killed romance?
Terrorism.
Well, NOW THE GUY CAN'T CHASE THE GIRL
TO THE AIRPORT anymore like in the
movie.
[laughter]
[applause]
He's got to sit outside at the curb
TEXTING HER, "I'VE DECIDED I LOVE YOU."
[laughter]
"YOU'RE THE ONE, BUT YOU NEED to come
out cuz I can't get past security."
[applause]
"Damn it, there's a cop behind me. Okay,
I've got to go to the cell phone waiting
lot."
"When you come out, text me and I'll
SWOOP IN JUST LIKE IN THE MOVIES with
the flowers."
We can't be what you want us to be. You
want that romantic guy, the big proposal
so you can tell your friends. Girls love
to tell their friends about exciting
things, right? Every girl First of all,
women are very smart cuz they work
together as a group.
[laughter]
And every girl has a little subgroup.
YOU HAVE A COMMITTEE. EVERY GIRL HAS A
COMMITTEE. And when SHE GOES OUT ON A
DATE, SHE COMES HOME, the committee HAS
A LOT OF QUESTIONS.
[laughter]
ALL WE HAVE IS ONE FRIEND. He just wants
to SEE A PICTURE.
[applause]
NO GUY HAS EVER COME HOME FROM A DATE
and his friends are like, "TELL ME ALL
ABOUT IT. WHAT WAS SHE LIKE? DOES SHE
HAVE ANY HOBBIES? IS SHE CLOSE TO THEIR
FAMILY?" NO, GET TO THE PICTURE.
"And does she have any cute friends I
can date?"
They want romance, the proposal. You
ever see somebody propose that you don't
know?
Isn't that weird? I was out to eat at a
fancy restaurant.
Sitting there
at the fancy restaurant, having a good
time. I'm, you know, sitting there with
Marshmallow. So, uh
[laughter]
there's some pressure from her committee
and uh
the guy next to me decides to ruin the
night by proposing.
[laughter]
And he couldn't get the ring out. THIS
STUPID F-150 GUY didn't rehearse getting
the ring out. It was STUCK IN HIS
POCKET. HE'S SWEATING LIKE I AM. HE'S
LIKE, "UH I HAVE A QUESTION." I'M LIKE,
"THIS GUY'S HAVING A SEIZURE."
[laughter]
ALL THE WOMEN KNEW WHAT WAS GOING ON
BECAUSE a proposal, THEY CAN
[laughter]
[applause and cheering]
THEY CAN SMELL IT FROM MILES AWAY. IT'S
A PROPOSAL. SOMEBODY'S DREAM IS COMING
TRUE OVER HERE. OVER HERE. COME ON IN.
GET THE BOXES OF TISSUES.
[laughter]
EVERY GUY IN THE PLACE was like, "I
don't need this tonight."
[applause]
So, now we all turn to watch the big
moment. The guy got on his knee,
proposed, and she said no.
OH, IT'S THE GREATEST THING I'VE EVER
SEEN.
[cheering]
[applause]
I'VE NEVER BEEN HAPPIER TO BE THAT CLOSE
TO SOMEBODY'S LOWEST POINT IN THEIR
LIFE.
I WAS LIKE, "GET IN THE HOLE. GET IN THE
HOLE. GET IN THE HOLE."
[applause]
I DIDN'T THINK IT COULD GET ANY BETTER
AND THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN THE WAITER
STARTED COMING OUT WITH A SPARKLY CAKE.
He had TO DO A U-TURN. He's like, "ABORT
THE MISSION. ABORT THE MISSION. ABORT
THE MISSION. ABORT THE MISSION."
[applause]
HOW DID THE GUY NOT KNOW? HOW DID the
guy not know? How did the guy not know?
How did the guy not know? Women let you
know when they want something. YOU DON'T
TELL US OUTRIGHT. You like to play a
little game called hint, you figure it
out.
[laughter]
And you better figure it out. Like a
woman doesn't ask to move into your
house. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. She
starts a little pile in the corner.
Then they want a drawer. I picture them
sitting around with a committee going,
"Did you get a drawer yet? DID YOU GET A
DRAWER YET?
Did you take your toothbrush and spike
it in the bathroom like we did the flag
on the moon? I AM HERE."
[laughter and applause]
THEN they take their hairs AND THEY
THROW THEM ALL OVER THE PLACE.
MY [cheering] KITCHEN, MY BATHROOM, MY
SEALANT.
[laughter]
[applause]
[cheering]
GOD CREATED WOMAN'S HAIR so men don't
cheat.
[laughter]
We love you women, but we could never be
what you want us to be. We're just too
simple. We're not smart. When we meet
women, you know what we do? We try and
change YOU OVERNIGHT.
[laughter]
WOMEN KNOW YOU CAN'T CHANGE A PERSON,
RIGHT? That's right, but you can BREAK
THEM.
THAT'S WHAT THEY DO. THEY TAKE YEARS.
THEY FIND A GUY THAT IS GOOD ENOUGH AND
THEY chisel him down. They chisel and
chisel and [cheering] chisel and chisel
and chisel and chisel
[applause]
and chisel and chisel. AND DON'T WEAR
THE HAWAIIAN SHIRT TO THE COMEDY SHOW.
[applause]
WHY DO YOU THINK GUYS like mowing the
lawn so much?
We'd rather hear aaaaaaaam
than whatever you have to say.
It's the same reason you guys blow dry
your hair for so long. It can't TAKE
THAT LONG. YOU PROBABLY KEEP WETTING
YOUR hair so you can stay in there. I
can't take another word from him.
Why do you think that thing is SHAPED
LIKE A GUN?
[laughter]
HE WON'T SHUT UP.
WE LOVE YOU WOMEN, BUT WE CAN'T BE what
you want us to be. We try. WE CAN'T
FIGURE YOU OUT. YOU'RE TOO DELICATE. YOU
GUYS ARE LIKE that string of Christmas
tree lights where if one of the bulbs IS
OUT, THE WHOLE [laughter] OPERATION IS
DOWN.
[applause]
YOU MAKE ONE MISTAKE, SHE just shuts
down and you don't know which bulb it
is.
You have to guess, IS THIS THE PROBLEM?
IS THIS THE PROBLEM? IS THIS THE
PROBLEM? IS THIS the problem? Is this
the problem? Is this the problem? Is
this the [cheering] problem?
[applause]
Is this the problem? Is this the
problem? Is this Is this Is this Is this
Is this Is this Is this Is this Is this
[cheering] Is this Is this
[applause]
And the dumb man is like, screw it. I'll
just go buy a new one. [laughter] I'm
sorry.
[cheering]
What I'm trying to tell you women is is
get married as close to your death as
possible.
[laughter]
Men actually get better with age. IT'S
BIOLOGICAL. YOU WANT to know what
happens as you get older?
All of a sudden, the TV commercials
start TALKING TO YOU.
[laughter]
RIGHT NOW, YOU DON'T HEAR THEM. ONE DAY
YOU'LL BE SITTING AROUND. It's like, are
you a male over the age of 40?
That's
That's me. WHAT'S GOING ON? IS
EVERYTHING OKAY?
DO YOU NOT HAVE AS MUCH ENERGY AS you
used to have? NO, I'M EXHAUSTED. WHAT IS
IT?
DO YOU STILL PRINT STUFF? YES, I DO.
[applause]
YOU MIGHT HAVE A TREATABLE CONDITION
CALLED LOW T. LOW T LOW TESTOSTERONE.
THEY'RE MAKING UP.
[laughter]
THIS IS LIKE GLUTEN AND SANTA CLAUS. IT
DOESN'T EXIST.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS TO MEN AS WE GET
OLDER. IT'S NATURAL AND THEY TALK ABOUT
IT LIKE IT'S A BAD THING. LOW T is the
greatest thing TO HAPPEN TO MEN.
EVERY
EVERY [cheering and applause]
EVERY EVERY BAD decision I ever made WAS
ON HIGH T.
[applause]
[cheering]
LOW T IS A BLESSING. High T destroys
lives.
[laughter]
Nothing bothers low T man. I'm driving,
somebody flips me off in traffic, low T
guy JUST KEEPS GOING.
[applause]
I GO OUT ON A DATE. I don't think SHE
LIKES ME. GREAT. I'LL get it out of THE
SLATE TONIGHT.
[laughter]
[applause]
YOU WANT TO BE HAPPY? LOWER YOUR BAR.
We'll lower our T. Let's meet halfway.
We can do it.
[applause]
THANK YOU.
[cheering]
[applause]
IT'S IT'S IT'S BEEN A LONG ROAD AND I I
really I can't thank everybody enough
who who's been here for me and uh I I
thank you so much.
[cheering]
[applause]
[applause and cheering]
[music]